## Lee Shu Cheng, Hadi

+65 87920504

leeshuzheng@gmail.com

User Experience Developer with a strong background in emerging front end web technologies and coordinating organisational practices across vertical teams. As a lead developer in a Big Four firm, he focuses on high fidelity prototyping and delivering sensible user experiences to end users. Adjacent to his profession, his passions lie in independent record label management and marketing albums digitally for local bands.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Ernst & Young (Acquired Adelphi Digital in Nov 18) UX Developer Jan 2018 - Ongoing

- Scaled and extended functionalities for NParks' One Million Trees program on trees.sg
- Top performer in Q3 2019
- Spearheaded revamp and maintenance project for government sector portfolio with 15 websites worth value of \$250,000
- Strengthened the Science Centre website build, winning best User Experience in the 2018
  Stevie Award
- Improved in writing accessible and semantic HTML as part of gov.sg's Digital Service Standards

Wunderfauks Sep 2016 - Dec 2017

Front End Web Developer

- Led nation-wide digital campaigns by leveraging on interactive user flows powered by Javascript, participated by over half a million users in total
- Strategised and implemented a revamp of company website

SAP SE Summer 2016

Front End Web Developer (Internship)

• Implemented a graphic user interface in AngularJS and Bootstrap for administrators to review over 200,000 feedback submissions by end users for novel Machine Learning platform

## **EDUCATION**

## National University of Singapore

Singapore 2013 - 2017

B.Soc.Sci. (Hons.) Communications and New Media SKILLS

WORKING KNOWLEDGE: HTML5/CSS3, SASS, Jade, ES5/6 JavaScript (jQuery, React Framework), PHP, Gulp, Grunt, Wordpress, Git Workflow, Adobe Illustrator CS6

BASIC KNOWLEDGE: Python, MongoDB

LANGUAGES: English (Fluent), Mandarin Chinese (Fair)